因为没有什么比你坐在那不出声
Because nothing irks me more than
更能让我烦躁不安的了
having you sitting there simmering.
上帝禁止我激怒你
God forbid I should irk you.
说出来吧  你有话要说
Well, just spit it out. You've got something to say.
伟大的杰克·科沃基恩  还是你更了解
The great Jack Kevorkian. You know better.
-没错  -没有什么能阻碍你的目的
- That's right. - Nothing gets in the way of the mission.
目的  什么目的
The mission? What mission.
这就是你说的省着用吗
Is that what you call rationing,
给一个可怜的老头脑袋上缠破胶带吗
Taping a fucking sheet of plastic around a poor guy's head?
我们应该再等等把气攒足
We should've waited till we had more gas.
我想知道那得等到猴年马月
Oh, and when would that have been I wonder?
我就该坚持
I should've insisted.
他  他  他  他已经去了
He was-- he was-- he was-- he was done.